i haven't been able to keep much down
lately and i just don't have any energy
and he's been this way for nearly a week
already
that all sounds pretty nasty and i know
you need to get back to school
i'm going to prescribe you something
that will take care of this right away
we'll have you back to normal in no time
did you know that a prescription alone
does not permit use of a prohibited
substance
we really appreciate you taking care of
devin so quickly
thanks doc i can't afford to be sick i
cannot miss my game next week
did you check though
remember that even if someone else gives
an athlete a prohibited substance
without their knowledge the athlete is
ultimately responsible for what goes on
and in their body
visit globaldro.com
[Music]
you